Come on, get in! Let's go!
We are Yuno Suzuki, the stalwart of the roadside tools, Iginari Talk!
Hello, everyone. I'd like to dance here by myself today.
It's not that I'm embarrassed... it's not like that.
I think I've been saying "I love that" since I was in middle school.
Do you remember? Ramen noodles!
No, you see, I've always said I liked cars.
He always mentioned the company's Mercedes-Benz and Lamborghini.
I always mention the names of luxury cars.
Even if he doesn't like cars anymore, he always said he wanted to ride in a convertible and drive a Mercedes.
So today, I'd like to ride in a go-kart.
That's a lie!
Yes, let's be serious.
Mmm-hmm, mm-hmm...
Well, I, Yuna Hazuki.
I went to driving school, which has been my dream for 7 years!
Yes!
So, let's see...
I went to driving school...
But that's not all!
Today is my final exam!
Yes!
Nobody's here.
Today is the final exam!
And it's just a written exam!
So I've already passed the skills test.
I've already passed the skills test.
If I pass the written exam today.
I can get my driver's license on the same day.
So you can drive today!
I already have a provisional license.
I got that one too.
I'm a saver, Burke!
If I get my license today...
I'd like you to open the Mercedes
I'd like you to open the car for me.
I'd like to put a beginner's mark on it
I'd like to put a beginner's mark on my Mercedes Benz and drive it.
I just ripped it open.
They're going to put this on.
If I get my license today.
I think I'd be driving all evening.
I think I'll be driving.
I'm going to go to Tokyo now.
I'm going to have the desire to drive
I don't drive a Hiace.
a convertible or a car with a sunroof.
I'm going to get in a car
I have one person convertible or sunroof
The rest is.
Maehama.
The street of palm trees
I want to make it bigger.
When I get good at driving
I want to do that.
What's it called?
Drifting.
But it's not a manual.
I wonder if I can do it.
It's my last exam.
Please support me!
I'm sure I'll be able to do it.
Thank you very much.
The end.
I have arrived at the license center!
All I have to do now is to go over here by myself and take the test.
Well, I just have to go to the reception desk and take the test.
I was feeling very strong, but I'm nervous.
I was feeling nervous.
But I can do it! Maybe. Maybe, I mean definitely.
I'm sure I'll be skipping when I come back here.
So, everyone, please wait for a moment to see me skipping out of here.
I'm gonna pass!
Aah! I'm off!
The test is over.
I already know which one is the synthetic leather.
Which one is it?
Passed!
I passed!
That's great!
I'm so relieved!
I am so happy! I've always wanted a driver's license.
I think I'm going to start driving today.
I'm sure I'll be driving around a lot.
If you see a car...
Yuna is probably driving it.
Yes!
That's why
I have a present for you!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, no!
A steering wheel case?
I'm so happy!
It's the first time I got a steering wheel case.
Thank you very much.
Well then...
I'll go to Abekatsu and buy a car.
And buy a car too?
Let's take delivery of the car.
Oh no!Oh no!
Eh, looks good!
something
What is it?
Amazing
I'll drive with this.
Thank you
Yay!
What a novel gift!
What were you going to do if I didn't make it?
Oh, I knew you wouldn't come.
Yay!
I got it.
That's funny.
Some people buy these things.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I've never seen it before.
Well, I'll tell you what...
I've already passed, right?
After this
I have to take a photo
For my driver's license.
That's very important.
I hear some people have a black history with it.
You look so pretty in this picture.
Celebrities...
It's even in the news.
It's very important to have that photo taken.
I'm going to practice taking it now.
Applause.
But there's no place to take lighting photos around here.
So I'm going to practice by taking a self portrait.
You know what?
I heard that you're not supposed to pose for lighting photos.
Maybe I shouldn't even show my teeth.
But I think it looks better if I smile with my teeth showing.
When you show it to various people...
I mean...
I think it makes a better impression.
Is that wrong?
Let's start with the safe version.
Oh, that's a bad impression.
You look like you're going to sleep.
No, it's not good.
I think it should have more impact.
My passport is blonde.
So I want my driver's license to have a different impact.
Hmmm...
Oh, I think I know what you mean, oh, I'm going to enjoy life.
I think this is fine too, for me.
Oh, I see, I see. It's a lighting photo of a car.
I'll make a lighting photo of you driving.
Oh, I should have brought my sunglasses.
I look like I'm driving a bookie.
This could certainly be a good photo with things.
Here we go.
I can't do it.
I couldn't do the plastic hoop.
Ta-da!
It's from Tohoku.
It's good to pose as a Northeasterner, isn't it?
You know, have some pride.
Who would take a lighting photo with their tongue sticking out?
I think they're driving a red light.
Don't get caught.
Just a little.
Oh, I see.
A little bit.
Who does that?
His tongue is sticking out a little bit.
It's like it's always sticking out.
The version with the front teeth sticking out a little bit.
I feel like I'm just making a funny face.
Wait, what is it?
If you were Runchan, would you wear twintails?
She would!
But my driver's license won't be renewed for 3 years.
I'll be 19 this year.
I'll use it until I turn 22.
No, this is going to be black history.
It'll only take a day.
Let's just smile normally.
I'll just smile like Karen.
Then wear twin-tails?
I don't know. I can't decide.
I'd like to ask the photographer what kind of expression he likes.
I'd like to ask the photographer what he likes.
Do you like the front teeth? Do you want the bottom part to stick out a little? I'll ask him.
I'll ask him, and we'll decide.
Let's see what kind of lighting you get.
Enjoy!
We got it! Study!
So now I would like to disclose my address!
I got my license!
Yay!
From now on, when I'm asked to show that ID card
Not my insurance card, not my student ID card
I will show off my driver's license.
I've grown up!
My dream has come true since junior high school.Your dream has come true, hasn't it, since middle school?
By the way, I didn't use it.
Blonde hair...
Hmmm...
I've grown up!
Ride your car a lot from now on.
I'll be careful to drive safely
I'd like to drive the Hiace around a lot!
Yes!
Mission accomplished!
I'm going to pick up everyone now!
I wonder how they will react.
I didn't tell them I got my license.
There he is! There he is!
Oh my God!
It's a nerve-wracking moment of destiny.
Here we go!
Hey, guys!
Yana, you're driving.
What? You're right!
Really?
Yes!
What?
Congratulations!
She's so cute!
Congratulations so much!
That's so awesome!
Congratulations!
Come on, get in, let's go!
Yeah, get in, get in.
Congratulations!
That was awesome! Seriously!
Oh, my God!
Congratulations!
You made it!
I practiced 2 hours every night with my demon teacher for this!